Dream big.
Marty Supreme is a drama film directed by Josh Safdie.
.................
Marty Mauser, played by Timothée Chalamet.
Judy, played by Sandra Bernhard.
Glenn Nordmann, played by David Mamet.
Koto Endo, played by Koto Kawaguchi.
Béla Kletzki, played by Géza Röhrig.
Ram Sethi, played by Pico Iyer.
Marty Supreme is a 2025 American sports comedy-drama film directed by
Josh Safdie who co-wrote it with Ronald Bronstein.
Timothée Chalamet stars in the title role, with Gwyneth Paltrow, Odessa A'zion, Kevin
O'Leary, Tyler Okonma, Abel Ferrara, and Fran Drescher in supporting roles.
Set in the 1950s, the film is loosely based on
American table tennis player Marty Reisman.
Safdie and co-writer Bronstein began developing the film in 2018 after Safdie was gifted a copy of Marty Reisman's
1974 memoir, The Money Player: The Confessions of America's Greatest Table Tennis Champion and Hustler.
Safdie met with Chalamet in 2018 and offered him the lead role.
Following a multi-year development period, the project was officially announced in July 2024; it
marks Safdie's first solo directorial effort since The Pleasure of Being Robbed (2008).
Marty Supreme premiered as a "secret screening" at the 2025 New York
Film Festival on October 6, 2025, followed by a U.S.
theatrical release by A24 on December 25, where it received widespread acclaim.
The National Board of Review and the American Film Institute
named it one of the top ten films of the year.
The film received nine nominations at the 98th Academy Awards, including Best
Picture, Best Director (Safdie) and Best Actor (Chalamet).
It also earned three nominations at both the 83rd
Golden Globe Awards and 32nd Actor Awards.
Chalamet won a Golden Globe Award and Critics' Choice Award for his performance.
The film explores themes of new york city, london,
england, paris, france, cairo, capitalism.
The tone is emotional.